(upbeat music)
♪ I can't stand it, I
know you planned it ♪
♪ I'mma set it straight, this Watergate ♪
♪ I can't stand rockin' when I'm in here ♪
♪ 'Cause your crystal ball
ain't so crystal clear ♪
♪ So while you sit back and wonder why ♪
♪ I got this fuckin' thorn in my side ♪
♪ Oh my god, it's a mirage ♪
♪ I'm tellin' y'all, it's sabotage ♪
♪ So, so, so, so listen up,
'cause you can't say nothin' ♪
♪ You'll shut me down with
a push of your button ♪
♪ But, yo, I'm out and I'm gone ♪
♪ I'll tell you now, I keep it on and on ♪
♪ 'Cause what you see, you might not get ♪
♪ And we can bet, so
don't you get souped yet ♪
♪ Scheming on a thing, that's a mirage ♪
♪ I'm trying to tell
you now, it's sabotage ♪
♪ Why ♪
♪ Our backs are now against the wall ♪
♪ Listen all y'all, it's a sabotage ♪
♪ I can't stand it, I
know you planned it ♪
♪ I'mma set it straight, this Watergate ♪
♪ But I can't stand rockin'
when I'm in this place ♪
♪ Because I feel disgrace
because you're all in my face ♪
♪ But make no mistakes
and switch up my channel ♪
♪ I'm Buddy Rich when
I fly off the handle ♪
♪ What could it be, it's a mirage ♪
♪ You're scheming on a
thing, that's sabotage ♪